export const questions = [
{
    question: "What is the name of the latest Nintendo system?",
    answer1: "Playstation",
    answer2: "Switch",
    answer3: "Xbox",
    answer4: "Wii",
    correct: "Switch",
},
{
    question: "When did the first Super mario bros release?",
    answer1: "1985",
    answer2: "1984",
    answer3: "1986",
    answer4: "1987",
    correct: "1985",
},
{
    question: "What was the first Souls-like game Developed?",
    answer1: "Dark Soul's",
    answer2: "Bloodborne",
    answer3: "Elden Ring",
    answer4: "Demon Soul's",
    correct: "Demon Soul's",
},
{
    question: "Who is the main character of The Legend of Zelda series?",
    answer1: "Zelda",
    answer2: "Ganon",
    answer3: "Link",
    answer4: "Tingle",
    correct: "Link",
},
{
    question: "What company publised the Metal Gear Series?",
    answer1: "Konami",
    answer2: "Square Enix",
    answer3: "Nintendo",
    answer4: "Kojima",
    correct: "Konami",
},
{
    question: "What game's main character is named Chel?",
    answer1: "Half-Life",
    answer2: "TF2",
    answer3: "Portal",
    answer4: "Deadlock",
    correct: "Portal",
},
{
    question: "Who was the last 'Warchief of the Horde?'",
    answer1: "Thrall",
    answer2: "Rexxar",
    answer3: "Sylvanas",
    answer4: "BlackHand",
    correct: "Sylvanas",
},
{
    question: "What game series are the 'Blades of chaos from?'",
    answer1: "God of War",
    answer2: "Diablo",
    answer3: "Dark soul's",
    answer4: "Hades",
    correct: "God of War",
},
{
    question: "What is the 151 pokemon in the pokedex?",
    answer1: "Pikachu",
    answer2: "Mew",
    answer3: "Mewtwo",
    answer4: "Bulbsaur",
    correct: "Mew",
},
{
    question: "What elder Scrolls game was released in 2011?",
    answer1: "Daggerfall",
    answer2: "Oblivion",
    answer3: "Morrowind",
    answer4: "Skyrim",
    correct: "Skyrim",
},
{
    question: "What was Toby Fox's first game?",
    answer1: "EarthBound",
    answer2: "Deltarune",
    answer3: "Undertale",
    answer4: "Celeste",
    correct: "Undertale",
},
{
    question: "What game has a loonie tunes art style?",
    answer1: "Cuphead",
    answer2: "It takes Two",
    answer3: "Noita",
    answer4: "Pikmin",
    correct: "Cuphead",
},
{
    question: "what series does the Character 'Samus' come from?",
    answer1: "mass effect",
    answer2: "F-Zero",
    answer3: "Metroid",
    answer4: "StarFox",
    correct: "Metroid",
},
{
    question: "Cloud is the main character of what Final fantasy?",
    answer1: "VIII(8)",
    answer2: "VII(7)",
    answer3: "X(10)",
    answer4: "VI(6)",
    correct: "VII(7)",
},
{
    question: "Who is kirbys bandana wearing friend?",
    answer1: "King Deedee",
    answer2: "MetaKnight",
    answer3: "Waddle Dee",
    answer4: "Waddle Doo",
    correct: "Waddle Dee",
},
];